IL Cafe we have you
covered hello and welcome to Il Cafe my
name is shidel and today we have an
episode that's going to dwell on this
phrase that captures a lot of
imaginations and for the right reasons
because it is indeed uh an effort to
empower customers anywhere cashless and
I've decided to figure out what this new
offering from the ICS Lombard universe
is all about it's a new innovation
indeed for health insurance Poli holders
and to help understand its benefits a
little bit better I've got with me an
expert from the ICI Lombard family and
that is shelish Du shales thank you so
much for joining us and welcome to the
show oh thank you thank you sh and
indeed it's my pleasure to join the your
show and uh give my input on that yeah
let's quickly get started with the
definition right would be useful for our
viewers to understand exactly what you
mean by anywhere cashless and how it is
how is it different from the other
different you know health insurance
offering certainly sh anywhere cash is a
facility under the policy where the
policy holder of ICC Lombard can take a
treatment in any hospital at pan India
level so uh in short uh now there is a
no restriction of hos netork hospital
for taking a treatment a customer can go
to anywhere in India and he or she can
off for cashless treatment in any
hospital so this is a unique feature of
anywhere
cashless Okay so What specifically what
benefits uh shell does anywhere cashus
offer to policy holders in terms of the
choice of hospital and also the
convenience or ease of uh you know
operating this if you talk about the
benefit there is no limitation of
hospital now customer can go to any
Hospital uh whether whether it is nearby
to their house or irrespective of any
speciality of the hospital so it's like
a paradigm shift in the entire Insurance
business uh where customer can get to
only hospital and take a treatment so
this is a unique feature of anywh Cas
now uh how does this particular you know
Innovation anyway caselist eliminate the
worries that are associated with some of
the upfront payments that need to be
made during hospitalization in Shish if
you see the features of anywhere
cashless or the cash list is like
customer need not to pay anything from
their pocket so in in the cash lless
facility customer can get into the
hospital take a treatment and at a time
of discharge they need not to worry
about the money
everything is is handled by the
insurance company so this is a payment
part where customer need not to worry
about anything paying from their pocket
mhm and what about the other side the
claims you know part Etc because I'm
sure there are hassles along the entire
chain of events that people normally you
know face so how does this really
anywhere cist help the entire process
okay so uh actually what happen in
anywhere Cashers the customer can skip
the cumbersome process of submitting
your document and waiting for for their
claim approval and getting for their
money from the insurance company so with
this anywhere cashless uh entire this
traditional way of claim submission like
sending their physical document to the
insurance company and uh following up
with the insurance company for their
payment it it will get eliminated with
the with the features of anywhere
cashless now in anywhere cash list
customer need to go to the hospital they
need to uh they need to inform to the
insurance company to the ICC Lombard and
post that everything will be Tak Care by
the ICC Lombard uh so customer need not
to worry about anything apart from that
yeah just needs to focus on getting
better right if you're indeed the
customer who's availing the service
yourself uh but yeah this places usually
in other situations right a lot of
strain on somebody's U state of uh
wellbe because a you are in the
situation B then you have to an entire
human being from the family has to be
deployed for
just tasks right and you to
say type of can you know go to school
and do what he has to do a college or
whatever and uh clearly that's what I'm
hearing from you now what are the steps
if you could break down the steps for
our viewers in terms of policy holders
availing of the N cist Service uh what
are the things that we need to remember
okay so there is some Elementary uh
condition like for availing anywhere
cashless facility the first customer
need to inform to ICC Lombard within uh
prior to 24hour First that is a
condition number one for availing a
cashless anywhere cashless uh customer
can go to our app Al take care app uh
there is a section called Health
assistance where they can go and they
can opt for anywhere cashless option
over there after opting the option then
the person from Lombard will connect
with the customer or connect with the
hospital to arranging the cash L to the
customer so this is a basic simple step
which customer need to follow and uh
after getting intimation at our in from
the customer side uh everything will be
taken care from ICC and after following
with the hospital and after having Award
with the customer for arranging the cash
now to come to the benefits like
long-term benefits I usually ask this
question only from the point of view of
you know policy holders but I'm going to
twist that around a little bit and I
want to know what's in it for IC lumbar
also why would something like anywhere
cashless help an organization that
offers the service and also the policy
holders who available yeah so for the
organization if you see somewhere uh we
want to serve our customer and we want
to provide a quity services to our
customer and based on our analysis and
Survey so what we found out most of the
customer they are they are preferring to
the hospital of their choice so with the
help of anywhere cashless now we can
provide a uh choice of Hospital of the
customer and as a organization we are
getting a uh intimation from the
customer side and uh based on that uh we
can we can enhance our services in the
hospital and we can we can ask the
hospital to provide a best care to our
customer so if you talk about the
organization in organization in long
term uh the customer satisfaction is the
one of the most important uh factor
which organization will get from this uh
facility any final words shales um in
closing any advice perhaps that you'd
like to give to anyone who's considering
ICC Lombard complete health insurance
and the anywhere cashless feature it
offers yeah so my only advice to
everyone who who's looking into the IC
Lombard health insurance policy the to
think about the facility of anywhere
cashless because it's a very very unique
features which is offered by ien Lombard
and uh somewhere customer is going to
get a lot of benefit from this feature
with a advice to the customer ke if they
want to utilize this Services they need
to inform to the insurance company
within 24 hours prior to their
hospitalization and as organization we
want this facility to be popularized uh
in the market and customer can use this
facility at a best m
interesting thank you so much for all
these pointers with respect to this
groundbreaking Innovation that icso
Lombard offers to people who are looking
at their own health and securing Peace
of Mind in that journey and he's wishing
all of you a very very good uh you know
sort of rest of the remaining months of
the year 2023 and uh continued good
health indeed and before you sign out
ches out of syllabus googly Wala
question coming up to you since we're
talking about anywhere cashless that
phrase is like you know suddenly in my
mind because I realized a lot of Life
generally is happening cashless only
nowadays do you remember going anywhere
suddenly saying that by it's a good
thing that life is cashless for me it
was U you know when I wanted to buy
suddenly there was Peru you know what
you call Amud or in Gujarati we call it
juk and suddenly I saw this was 10 bucks
I have 10 bucks in my wallet to give to
somebody and I was like Google pay here
and this happened when was the last
personal experience that you had using
some of these digital payments when you
least expected that you might have been
it I can I can say that digital payment
is a revolution in the entire payment
journey and and and it's giving a lot of
benefit to all the all the user not only
for me but all the citizen of India and
uh coming to your point I'm using uh
digital payment very very frequently so
it is not just only for purchasing per
or something like that yeah absolutely
that was just an example but you know
that is somehow it gives you MTI in your
head saying that oh is also possible for
10 10 Rupees you can actually use
digital payments but yeah the only
reason I brought this unrelated kind of
uh you know area over here because at
anywhere cashless is how I go outside
the house also cash list sometimes but
nice to have spoken of it in the context
of insurance offerings at ICS chish
thank you so much for your time and here
is wishing you the best of health as
well you're most welcome and thanks for
my S